Pencil, watch this!
Hah! Isn't that just so funny?
Absolutely not, Firey!
I've seen Bubble pop quite a number of times,
but that right there was by far the cruelest.
And you know, Firey? I think you
need a taste of your own medicine.
Ahhh!
Pencil! Don't tell me you just killed Firey!
Out of my way!
Pencil:
And I'm tired of you guys, too!
- Huh?
- Ruh... ruh... rugle...
- Augh!
- BWUH!
Oh no!
Hi, Pencil! Are you glad that I didn't vomit on you?
Whoa! You can speak again?
Doesn't that feel weird after fifteen months of silence?
Bleh!
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Spongy, Firey, and Pencil, you were up for elimination.
We'll see who will be eliminated at the
Cake at Stake Ceremony.
We have a cake this time.
It's a collection of shovels.
Excuse me, but how are shovels cakes?
Well, they're caked with mud, so they're cakes.
If you're safe, you'll get a cake.
One person won't receive a cake and will be eliminated.
Announcer:
Ice Cube, Rocky, David, Bubble, and Leafy
were not up for elimination, so they all get cakes.
Are you rejecting my cakes?
That makes me want to cry, and I cry acid.
Wah, wah, wah!
- Ahhhh!
- Hmph!
- Aw, seriously?!
Anyways, 464 people voted for either Spongy, Firey,
or Pencil to be eliminated.
Announcer:
Firey, you only got 64 votes, so you're safe. Fling!
Catch!
See, I like your cake!
Hulal-lal-luh!
Announcer:
Pencil,
in episode 15, you were the
only contestant who never got a vote.
I remember that.
For this episode, you received 259 votes,
which is the most ever, you are eliminated.
What?!
This machine thingy must be broken!
Oh well, Pencil was such a menace anyway.
Oh no! Ice Cube, with Pencil gone,
our alliance is too small. What do we do?
Needy's got to join!
People, quiet down.
You are now the final 7.
That's so few, I can count it on one hand.
Jeez, no need to brag!
Anyway, since you have made it so far,
you all get a reward.
- David: Seriously?
- Everyone else: Yeah?
Teddy bears! Every point you currently
have is traded for one teddy bear...
[Everyone praises]
...but reaching the final 7 also means a
new stage in the battle.
Everyone:
Gasp!
That means no more points.
The 19th contest is a unicycle race.
Announcer:
The first three people to finish the course
will receive immunity.
The rest will be up for elimination.
- Go.
- Gah!
- Firey: Woah! Oh no, I can't balance!
- David: Aw, seriously?!
- Bubble: Woah, oh no! Oooh!
Ahhh!
I think I'm getting... the hang of it.
Come on, Ice Cube, you're coming with me.
I don't want you being friends with
that backstabbing Bubble.
Okay, I do not backstab!
Seriously, do you really think that bubbles can stab?
- Ice Cube: Ahhh!
- Leafy: Ah! Get away, get away! Before Bubble stabs us!
Leafy and Ice Cube:
Ahhhhh!
Um, the right way is that way...
Huh... Heheh-haoh... Uh...
Woah-oh! Ha-haohh! Wheee!
Ohhhh! Hah! Ah-ha, ha, haoh!!
Huh?
Ha-AHH!
No brakes, no brakes, no brakes! Ahh... ahhh..
Uhhh-hah-uhhh...
Huh-uhh... Oh.
Phew...
Th-th-that was close...way too close.
Ahhhhh!
Ha, ha. What a failure!
Oioh, oh, ohh-ho-ho! Haaah, oh, oh.
Bubble, you finished first, so you get immunity.
Yoylecake!
Bleh!
Rocky is also immune.
Now there is only one spot left for immunity.
Huh? One spot left? I'd better hurry up!
Aw, seriously?!
[slo-mo]
[in the tune of "Mary Had a Little Lamb"]
♪ Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh-ahh-ahh! ♪
♪ Ahh-ahh-ahh! ♪
♪ Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh-ahh-ahh-ahh! ♪
♪ Ahh, ahh, ahh-ahh-ahh! ♪
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Hnnngehhh-Hyuh!
Yay! I get immunity!
Yes, Firey. You do.
Would you like to see a magic trick?
Don't think I don't know what your
magic tricks are like. NO!
Well, too bad. Poof.
Oh, wait, that's not what I meant to do. Poof.
So you three have immunity, while you four don't.
Is that correct?
- Firey: Yeah, yeah! That's right, that's right!
- Bubble: You're correct! That is correct!
- Rocky: BLEH! BLEH! BLEH!
- Leafy: Y-yeah, y-you could believe that.
- Ice Cube: Ahhh!
- David: Aw, seriously?!
- Spongy: [mumbling]
- Leafy: You know, i-if you wanted to.
- Ice Cube: Ahhh!
- David: Aw, seriously?!
- Spongy: [mumbling]
- Leafy: Because... ohh... it's true...
- Ice Cube: Ahhh!
- David: Aw, seriously?!
- Spongy: [mumbling]
Bubble, since you finished first, you get another reward.
You get to choose a fourth person to have immunity.
Ohhh, o-okay. Uhhhh, Ice Cube,
- are we still in an alliance?
- NO!
Uhhh, then I'll give to Leafy
to prove to her that I'm a nice person after all.
Well, I guess that's somewhat nice but not extremely nice.
You've still got a lot of work to do
but at least it was a good effort.
Blah, blah, whatever.
So that leaves David, Spongy and
Ice Cube up for elimination.
Voters and viewers, subscribers and commenters,
trolls and flamers.
Vote off who you think should be eliminated
by commenting on this video.
Every vote counts, so please do vote.
Oh yeah, do not forget to watch Episode 20
which comes out on August 1st, 2011.